buyv2cigs.co.uk 2016-06-30

# Privacy Policy : BuyV2Cigs

We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we have adopted this Privacy Policy. Our Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and explains data collection and use practices for the BuyV2Cigs website. The BuyV2Cigs website includes all web pages, newsletters, discussion forums and lists and opt-in announcement lists owned and/or operated by BuyV2Cigs. By accessing our website, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Privacy Policy.

We promise that we will use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy as follows-

**What information are you collecting and how are you collecting it?**

**Do you collect IP addresses?**  
Every computer connected to the Internet is given a set of numbers, that serve as that computer's IP ("Internet Protocol") address.

When a visitor requests a page from any Web site within our network of sites, our Web servers automatically recognize that visitor's IP address (and possibly a domain name associated with the IP address). The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our Sites.

We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, and to investigate misuse of our network, its users, or to cooperate with law enforcement.

We do not collect and evaluate this information for specific individuals.

Our Web servers do not automatically record e-mail addresses of the visitors.

**What are cookies?**  
From time to time, we may send a "cookie" to your computer.

A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can not read data off of your computer hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system.

We use cookies to identify which areas of our website you have visited and to store your current purchases until you clear your shopping cart.

You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your Internet browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent.

If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our Site and other Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.

**How do you use single-pixel gifs?**  
We may use single-pixel gif images, sometimes referred to as web beacons, to count Web page accesses and gather some general statistical information.

We do not gather personal information through the use of these images.

**What personal information do you collect?**

We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties.

Wherever we collect personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy.

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. The personal information we collect may include your name, title, e-mail address, phone number and business.

We may request your e-mail address or mailing address for the purposes of conducting a contest or to provide additional services (for example, subscriptions to announcement lists or information about conferences and trade shows).

Participation in contests or other promotions on our network is completely voluntary and you have a choice whether or not to disclose personal information.

Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as PostCodes). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes.

We may also offer access to some services that require registration. We may use your registration contact information to send notification to you of products and services by e-mail and/or postal mail. We **will not** share that information with our clients. We may, however, use your IP address internally and share it with third parties.

When you use co-branded services, or those provided by a third party, within our Network, your information may be passed to the co-brand or third party provider and their use of your information is subject to their applicable privacy policies.

We may from time to time send you an e-mail announcing new products and services. If you choose to supply your postal address in an online form, you may receive postal mailings from us.

**Will you disclose the information you collect to outside third parties?**  
We will disclose personal information and/or an IP address:

> 1) When required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to:   
>  a) Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities and conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on us ;  
>  b) Protect and defend the rights or property of our network of sites and related properties, or visitors to our network of sites and related properties;   
>  c) Identify persons who may be violating the law, our terms of use and Web site User Agreement, the rights of third parties, or otherwise misusing our network or its related properties;   
>  2) When we have your consent to share the information;   
>  3) When you use co-branded services within our network of sites, you grant us permission to pass your registration information back to that service partner. Their use of your information is subject to their applicable privacy policies.

We maintain a strict "No-Spam" policy that means that we **do not** sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third-party, without your consent or as permitted by this Privacy Policy.

**What else should I know about my privacy when online?**

Our network of websites may contain hyperlinks to third party Web sites,  We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party Web sites or advertisers. We do not share any of the individual personal information you provide us with the third parties to which we link, except as stated elsewhere within this Privacy Policy, although we may share general, aggregate data with such third parties (for example, how many people use our website).

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example through e-mail, discussion lists, or elsewhere - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your personal information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.

**Your Consent To This Agreement**  
By using our network of websites, you consent to the collection and use of information by us as specified above. We reserve the right to modify this Policy in the future. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we would disclose it.

(Last revised 29th April 2014)
